[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1902 the first movie house opened in the USA, in this city.", "correct_answer": "Los Angeles", "incorrect_answers": ["Menlo Park", "Pittsburgh", "New York City"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of rock is the white marble used to build the Taj Mahal?", "correct_answer": "Metamorphic", "incorrect_answers": ["Ore", "Sedimentary", "Igneous"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Disney animated feature film is this quote from: Im telling you, you gotta help me! Dont leave me here! Im in hillbilly hell! My IQs dropping by the second! Im becoming one of them! ?", "correct_answer": "Cars", "incorrect_answers": ["Treasure Planet", "The Aristocats", "Toy Story"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The capital city of what country is called Quito?", "correct_answer": "Ecuador", "incorrect_answers": ["Bolivia", "Macedonia", "Yemen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Charles Dickens made the following statement about beer: It was as natural as eating and to me as necessary, and I would not have thought of eating a meal without drinking beer.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sangria is a drink, traditionally served at Mexican weddings. Sangria contains all these ingredients, except one.", "correct_answer": "Tequila", "incorrect_answers": ["Fruit juice", "Brandy", "Wine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What makes the Scarlet Macaw, a parrot species indigenous to South America, unsuitable for a pet?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["It is very demanding.", "It is extremely noisy.", "It is a high maintenance pet."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This dog breed, considered one of the first sighthound dog breeds, has very long fur and is quite tall, with long legs and ears.", "correct_answer": "Afghan Hound", "incorrect_answers": ["Canadian Pointer", "Bolognese", "Airedale Terrier"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This fictional character from Pirates of the Caribbean made the following statement: I make a point of avoiding familiarity with pirates.", "correct_answer": "Will Turner", "incorrect_answers": ["Elizabeth", "Jack Sparrow", "Commodore Norrington"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which hat is a distribution of the Linux operating system?", "correct_answer": "Red Hat", "incorrect_answers": ["Black Hat", "White Hat", "Blue Hat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Greek goddess, daughter of Zeus and Metis, is the virgin patron of Athens. The Parthenon was built as her temple.", "correct_answer": "Athena", "incorrect_answers": ["Aphrodite", "Hera", "Venus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Testosterone is a male hormone secreted in the testes in males and ovaries in females. Its deficiency is related to various disorders such as this one.", "correct_answer": "Alzheimer\u2019s Disease", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Blindness", "Melanoma"]}]